
// Array of objects
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which of these is a paint made from pigments and plastic?" ,
        options: ['Acrylic','Gesso','Acetone', 'Tempera'],
        answer: 'Acrylic'
      },
    
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Early photographers made their images on which of these materials?",
        
        options:['Glass','Stone',' Paper',' Plastic'],
        answer: 'Glass'
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:'To which artistic movement does Paul Gauguin’s The Yellow Christ belong?',
        options:['Impressionism','Bauhaus','Cloisonnism','Fauvism'],
        answer: 'Cloisonnism'
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:'What does the Venus of Brassempouy represent?',
        options:['a woman’s head','an angel','a human figure','an old man'],
        answer: 'a woman’s head'
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:'Which architect founded the Bauhaus school of design?',
        options:['Walter Gropius','Frank Gehry',' I.M. Pei',' Frank Lloyd Wright'],
        answer: 'Walter Gropius'
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:'Who designed the Vietnam Veterans Memorial?',
        options:['Henri Matisse','Maya Lin','Frank Gehry','Frank Lloyd Wright'],
        answer: 'Maya Lin'
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:'Which one of these is not a well-known Indian sculptor?',
        options:['Ramkinkar Baij','Henry Moore','Kumaradeva','Krishna Reddy'],
        answer: 'Henry Moore'
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:' What animal often symbolizes peace in art?',
        options:['Dog','Duck','Deer','Dove'],
        answer: 'Dove'
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:'What was the subject of the earliest known paintings?',
        options:['Animals','Landscapes','Sports','Flowers'],
        answer: 'Animals'
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:'Which of these artists is famous for using human paintbrushes?',
        options:['Paul Cezanne',' Yves Klein','Giorgio Vasari','Jackson Pollock'],
        answer: ' Yves Klein'
    },
]